Guide to the Puebla Archives
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Civil Cases, 1567-1878; Series III
  - Records of Antonio de Lara, and Francisco de Quebara, 1757 (Box 32, Folder 677)
  - María Pasquala de los Santos and María Franca, Indians, vs. their husbands for incontinence, 1757 (Box 32, Folder 678)
  - Mariano Pardo vs. Mariano Carranza, concerning a sum of money, 1758 (Box 32, Folder 679)
  - Appraisal of houses and farms belonging to José de Vargas, 1758 (Box 32, Folder 680)
  - Joséph Benites vs. Manuel de los Santos concerning payment of a debt, 1759 (Box 32, Folder 681)
  - Manuel Beltran vs. Joséph de Arellano concerning payment of a sum, 1760 (Box 32, Folder 682)
  - Juana Antonia de Loaessa vs. her husband Joséph Lujan for mistreatment, 1760 (Box 32, Folder 683)
  - Receipt executed by Manuel de Salazar y Velazco for his wife Marta Michaela de Bustamante Bustillo for an amount granted by Manuel Fernando Bustamante, 1760 - 1765 (Box 32, Folder 684)
  - Preparatory decrees concerning the inventory of and the division of the estate of the late Alferez don Ignacio López de Herrara, 1760 -1771 (Box 32, Folder 685)
  - Antonio Febrer vs. Joachin de Armigo and his bondsman, 1760 - 1775 (Box 32, Folder 686)
  - José Manuel Bonilla and his creditors, concerning bankruptcy, 1762 - 1768 (Box 32, Folder 687)
  - Capt. Pedro Gil de Tejada vs. José Pérez de Corcha concerning a sum of money, 1764-1779 (Box 32, Folder 688)
  - Joséph Camano vs. Antonio Espinosa de los Monteros concerning a sum of money, 1765 (Box 32, Folder 689)
  - Mariano Pardo vs. José de Garate concerning a sum of money, 1765 (Box 32, Folder 690)
  - Decree by Andrés de Urbina concerning notarization of deeds of his property, 1765 (Box 32, Folder 691)
  - Inventory and estimate of the estate of the late Miguél García Serrano, 1765 - 1771 (Box 32, Folder 692)
  - Cession of a house in the neighborhood of San Francisco Joséph by Diego García Solano, 1765-1799 (Box 32, Folder 693)
  - Francisco Xavier Benavides, attorney of the common people of Zacapoaztla, vs. the coadjustor of Zacapoaztla, for extreme punishments given to the Indians, 1767 (Box 32, Folder 694)
  - Juan de Santiago, Indian, vs. Joséph de Quintanilla concerning payment for services, 1770 (Box 32, Folder 695)
  - Sale of land by Petra Udaria to C. Dionicio Caceros, 1770 - 1837 (Box 32, Folder 696)
  - Petition by Juan Antonio Sesar to local authorities concerning his pulpería, 1773 (Box 32, Folder 697)
  - Inventory of the Estate of the laste Antonio Carpintero, 1774 (Box 32, Folder 698)
  - Testimony of the sale of my house at Hymantlam which was inherited from Michaela Duran de Huerta, 1775 (Box 32, Folder 699)
  - Petition by Antonio Alberto Fernández, executor for the late María Bárbara Miceses Altamirano, concerning her estate, until an heir be named, 1776 (Box 32, Folder 700)
  - Joséph Benito Gutiérrez, of Huesca vs. Pedro Cavallero concerning payment of a sum, 1776 (Box 32, Folder 701)
  - Documents concerning the sale of the hacienda of Santa Anna Xalmimilulcoy Rancho de Sr. San José, to José de Lastra, 1778 - 1789 (Box 33, Folder 702)
  - José Manuel de las Penas, of Huaguapan vs. Pedro Salgado, concerning accounting records, 1778 - 1791 (Box 33, Folder 703)
  - Joséph de Ortega Moro vs. Francisco Jauer de Gamboa, 1779 (Box 33, Folder 704)
  - José Bernal vs. Gabriel Bravo concerning a sum of money, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 705)
  - Joaquín de Cardenas vs. Joséf Berjel concerning payment of a debt, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 706)
  - Petition by Pedro de Escalona Matamoros that action on his case be sped up, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 707)
  - Petition by Justo Ramirez to local authorities concerning his pulpería, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 708)
  - Petition concerning the price of soap and lard by Joachim de Saldana y Bonilla for Antonio Barcina and other owners of pig-processing houses, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 709)
  - Petition by Isidro Vicente, Indian, that his wife be returned to him, 1780 (Box 33, Folder 710)
  - Action on petition of José Nicolás de Huerta, lieutenant of Justice of Hacofepco that Francisco del Real terminate debts with him, 1780 - 1783 (Box 33, Folder 711)
  - Inventory of the estate of José Bretón Fernández del Rocal, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 712)
  - José Francisco Palacios vs. Ignacio Martín concerning a sum of money, 1781 (Box 33, Folder 713)
  - Petition by José Antonio Monteray concerning a sum of money, 1782 (Box 33, Folder 714)
  - Rosa Fernández de San Miguél, acting for her son, Ignacio Mena vs. Carlos Fernández de Lara, 1784 (Box 33, Folder 715)
  - Petition by Gil Alonso Rodrigues and José Joaquín Guerrero concerning the imprisonment of several men for debts, 1782 (Box 33, Folder 716)
  - Petition by Ignacio Tello that he be released from prison, being sick, and account of his death, 1784 (Box 33, Folder 717)
  - Case against Ignacio Trujeque, imprisoned in Puebla, because of money owed to Joaquín Cosio, 1784 - 1785 (Box 33, Folder 718)
  - Inventory of the estate of the late Cristóbal de Mena, 1784 - 1792 (Box 33, Folder 719)
  - Decrees concerning citizens and commoners of San Bernardino Chalchehusran of Cholula, 1784 - 1799 (Box 33, Folder 720)
  - Petition by José La Sano Campos to local authorities concerning his store, 1785 (Box 33, Folder 721)
  - Petition by Pedro Rocha to local authorities concerning his store, 1785 (Box 33, Folder 722)
  - Decrees concerning the carrying out of the will of the late Antonio Anaya Cadiz, 1785 - 1786 (Box 33, Folder 723)
  - Manuel Zeron vs. Francisco Alvarez concerning payment of a debt, 1785 - 1786 (Box 33, Folder 724)
  - Mariano Barrios vs. Francisco Lisa concerning payment of a debt owed to his late father, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 725)
  - Maríano Miguél Carranza as executor for the Comc. Co. vs. several individuals concerning payment of a debt, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 726)
  - Antonia del Castillo y Canas vs. Juaquin José Castillo concerning a sum of money, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 727)
  - Pedro Luis Frias vs. Mariano Brillan concerning payment of a debt, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 728)
  - Inventory of the Estate of the late Manuel Hidalgo de la Torre, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 729)
  - Decrees concerning Ana de Orsilles to their chicken vendors vs. Antonia Martínez, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 730)
  - Ignacio María de Victoria Salazar y Frias vs. Miguél Sánchez concerning a sum of money, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 731)
  - Deed of sale of the hacienda and windmill of San Martín, sold in 14,000 pesos, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 732)
  - Augustín García de Villa Lobos, of Cuantla de las Amilpas vs. Francisco Carmen concerning a sum of money, 1786 (Box 34, Folder 733)
  - Action promoted by Rafael Fixier concerning sales tax of Huejozingo, 1786 - 1789 (Box 34, Folder 734)
  - Proceedings concerning bonds and transferrals of deposits in the power of Miguél de Santerbas, 1786 - 1791 (Box 34, Folder 735)
  - Inventory of the estate of the late Juan José del Solar, 1786 - 1787 (Box 34, Folder 736)
  - Decrees of sale by Tomás Hendez, from Hacienda de San Miguél, 1786 - 1803 (Box 34, Folder 737)
  - Joséfa de la Encarnacion vs. her husband Pascual Licona concerning his mistreatment of her, 1787 (Box 34, Folder 738)
  - Sale of San Miguél de las Palmillas, hacienda, 1788 (Box 34, Folder 739)
  - Mariano Gómez, tax collector, vs. Lorenzo Mayorsa concerning payment, 1788 - 1790 (Box 34, Folder 740)
  - The citizens of Huatinchan vs. Joséf Agustín Saldana, public scribe of Puebla concerning a sum of money, 1788 - 1793 (Box 34, Folder 741)
  - Petition to the General Advisor claiming right to inherit his grandfather's possessions (unsigned), 1789 (Box 34, Folder 742)
  - Concerning the sale of the hacienda of San Miguél de las Pamillas, belonging to José Rafael Granillo, auctioned by José Mariano Carracoy Villegas, 1789 (Box 34, Folder 743)
  - Petition by Juan Franco Regis asking that Micaela Covarruvias and her brother be imprisoned for transgressing several laws, 1790 (Box 34, Folder 744)
  - Andrés Xavier Uriare executor for the estate of Pedro Brito y Abrey, carrying out of the will, 1790 (Box 34, Folder 745)
  - Pascual Antonio vs. owner of J. Isidro concerning payment for services, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 746)
  - Hearings concerning confiscation of pulque of Juan Francisco Fernández Gill, José González, and Vicente Molano, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 747)
  - Case against Juan de Leon and Francisco Tello, bondsman of Juan García, concerning debt to the Royal Hacienda, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 748)
  - Hearing concerning 4 lbs. tobacco confiscated by the visiting lieutenant Benito de Ochoa, Pedro Masas, Marían Cardena, Francisco Villaverde, Juan Agesta and María Dolores, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 749)
  - Case of José Mariano Pena concerning tobacco, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 750)
  - Confiscation of 115 lbs. of tobacco from Mariano de Pina and Bernabe Matias by Alejandro Delgado for the city of Tepeaca, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 751)
  - Petition by Juan de la Torre concerning case against him, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 752)
  - Case concerning confiscation of 13-1/4 lbs. tobacco by Ignacio Torres, lieutenant of San Baltazar, no defendant, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 753)
  - Case of those guilty of confiscating tobacco, found in Amosoc by Juan Pedro Jurami, 1791 (Box 34, Folder 754)
  - José María Arauto vs. Antonio Alberto Fernández concerning payment of a debt, 1792 (Box 34, Folder 755)
  - Valuation of the property of Xacalon belonging to Máximo Dominguez, 1792 (Box 34, Folder 756)
  - José Miguél Falcon vs. José Espejo and Mariano Montfort concerning a hacienda, 1792 (Box 34, Folder 757)
  - Case against Juan Angel Huarte concerning a debt, 1792 (Box 34, Folder 758)
  - Petition by María Mathilde Linankis concerning the case lost by her husband, José Alonso de la Rosa, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 759)
  - Case presented by Pedro Mungiuia, executor for Miguél Masias Pliego, concerning intervention in the farms of Tacacho, Stapha, and San Nicolás, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 760)
  - Petition by Manuela Antonia Ovando vs. her husband for adultery, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 761)
  - Report concerning the estate of the late José Antonio Perez, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 762)
  - Petition by Andrés del Puerto Vicario concerning case against him by José Mineses professing his innocence, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 763)
  - Case against José Manuel Rinderos, from Amozoc concerning confiscation of 47 lbs. of tobacco denounced by an Indian of Chaphacac, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 764)
  - Case concerning tax collection of the priest of Zacatlan, José San Martín and his bondsman Juan Sanches de Tagle, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 765)
  - Proceedings concerning rebuilding of the Church of Santiago Nahuituxco, case presented by citizens of said town, 1792 (Box 35, Folder 766)
  - Petition concerning the case of Carrillo vs. Franco Hernández Díaz, present by the latter, 1793 (Box 35, Folder 767)
  - Petition by citizens of Cholula, concerning water rights, 1793 (Box 35, Folder 768)
  - Concerning confiscation of 10 lbs. of tobacco reported by Benito Ochoa, 1793 (Box 35, Folder 769)
  - Case against Pedro Guerra and Rafaela Cabanez, for incontinence presented by Gaspar Mejia, 1793 (Box 35, Folder 770)
  - Case concerning puppeteers in Teuzitlan presented by Domingo Antonio de la Torre, 1793 - 1794 (Box 35, Folder 771)
  - Pedro Antonio vs. Lorenzo de Santiago concerning a quarrel the latter initiated, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 772)
  - Petition by José Ignacio Cameros concerning inability to pay a debt, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 773)
  - José Antonio Campos vs. Teodor Algoden concerning payment of a debt, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 774)
  - Antonio de Cardenas vs. Antonio Solo, to fulfill his contract as a violinist, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 775)
  - Petition by Joaquín de Feran concerning debts he owed to Juan Domingo Villar, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 776)
  - Petition by José Antonio Flores to the Intendant concerning a debt owed him by Juan Francisco Gill, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 777)
  - Petition by executor for Mariano García concerning debt owed to him by Tomás Díaz, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 778)
  - Concerning petition of the Judge subdelegate, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 779)
  - Complaint by María Joséfa Medina, mother of José Ignacio Rojas concerning his being accused of taking María Serapia to Vera Cruz, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 780)
  - Pedro de Mier vs. José Berardo concerning inferior quality of purchase, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 781)
  - Proceedings concerning exchange of houses between Manuel Pérez and Francisco Bonilla, of San Salvador el Verda, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 782)
  - Petition by Joséph Rodríguez Ponton, scribe, that he be paid for services, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 783)
  - Petition by José Agustín de Saldana concerning his suit, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 784)
  - Gregorio Santos Iglesias vs. Isidrio de Bella for disregarding an order, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 785)
  - Petition by Manuel Sepeda that he be released from prison, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 786)
  - Petition by Melchora María that her husband Francisco Manuel Timoteo be released from prison, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 787)
  - Investiture of 500 ps on ranch belonging to Jesús Nazareno Tlayshualco in favor of FNC, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 788)
  - Petition by Manuel Valdivia concerning his store, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 789)
  - Sale of the hacienda San Antonio Atenco from Mariano García Salado to Diego Antonio Salis, 1794 - 1795 (Box 35, Folder 790)
  - Proceedings demanding that Antonio Cruzado of Huejozingo inform them of taxes owed, 1794 - 1797 (Box 35, Folder 791)
  - Deal between Miguél Sandovál and Estévan Munuera concerning 3,000 ps from a chaplaincy, 1794 - 1801 (Box 35, Folder 792)
  - Case against Feliciano Angel, Indian of Tlacotopec, concerning payment of taxes presented by José Díaz Pliego, 1794 - 1803 (Box 35, Folder 793)
  - Petition by Pedro Antonio, Indian, concerning a bull which ruined his crops, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 794)
  - Petition by José Bringas de Bringas Manzaneda concerning case against him by Antonio Hernandez, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 795)
  - Case concerning a declaration to be made about the sale of the Hacienda Santa Ana Xalminilulco by the Convent of the Carmelites, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 796)
  - Petition of José Feliciano concerning debts to Francisco Banos, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 797)
  - List of creditors to whom D. Vicente Fernández owes money, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 798)
  - Petition by José Carlos de Lagasca, now imprisoned for a debt owed to Lucas Velazques, that he be set at liberty, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 799)
  - Petition by José Martín, Indian, concerning Santiago Felipe's claim on his land, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 800)
  - Petition by Anna Pascuala and Juana Feliciana, Indians, that they be released from prison, as they will pay their debts, 1795 (Box 35, Folder 801)
  - Case concerning Don Cristóbal de Pay y Pinson, to render account of 2,192 pesos, 1795 (Box 36, Folder 802)
  - Case presented by the citizens of Santa María at Malacatepeque, Cholula vs. Santa Clara Ocoyucan concerning petition about the land of Stam, 1795 (Box 36, Folder 803)
  - Verdict against Juan de los Santos Cruz, 1795 (Box 36, Folder 804)
  - Action initiated by José Joaquín Serrano that his son José Cristóbal, having run away with a woman, be caught and punished, 1795 (Box 36, Folder 805)
  - Deal concerning a house of María Isabel de Leiba y Córdova, widow, as executor for her late husband, 1795 - 1797 (Box 36, Folder 806)
  - Petition by Catarina Joséfa Aguilar, Indian, that her son, José Mariano Hernández be released from prison, since he had been forced into his crime, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 807)
  - Petition by Ramon Alarcon, that he be informed about the release from prison of the judge, scribe and mayor, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 808)
  - Petition by Joséph Bernardo, Indian, concerning debt owed to Joséph Polo, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 809)
  - Statement and inventory of the estate of Antonio Camacho, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 810)
  - José Joaquín Campos vs. José Longinos, Indian, concerning a sum of money, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 811)
  - Case presented by María Gertrudis del Castillo asking to be allowed to return to her husband, Mariano Roman, from whom she has been separated, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 812)
  - Máximo Dominguez deed of purchase of a house, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 813)
  - Petition by Manuel Ignacio Gonzáles concerning case against him by Francisco Ruíz Adorno concerning a sum of money, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 814)
  - Petition by José Antonio Guemes concerning his notarized will, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 815)
  - Petition by Ignacia Gutiérrez del Solar for money to feed her child, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 816)
  - Complaint of Onofre Lorenzo Jaen against his wife Petra Catarina Serrano concerning her conduct, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 817)
  - Notarization of petition by Vicente Domingo Lombardin, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 818)
  - Petition by Luz Perez that she be allowed to leave her employment and return to Spain, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 819)
  - Petition by José María Ramirez that he be released from prison, as his children have smallpox, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 820)
  - Case presented by María Eusebia Ramirez concerning taking her husband out of the company of his brother, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 821)
  - Petition by Antonio de Sesina concerning rooms offered him in the Convent of the Nuns of the Conception, 1796 (Box 36, Folder 822)
  - Petition by Anastacio Chávez that he be released from prison, 1796 - 1797 (Box 36, Folder 823)
  - Petition by Joséph Joaquín de Montalvo that he not be punished for the violent behavior of his servant, 1796 - 1799 (Box 36, Folder 824)
  - Claim by María Ignacia Angelo concerning having asked that her husband, Ignacio Alvares, be imprisoned, 1796 - 1800 (Box 36, Folder 825)
  - Proceedings -investigation of 2 stores said to belong to Miguél Serrano, 1796 - 1803 (Box 36, Folder 826)
  - Juan Felles, represented by his sons vs. Martín Francisco and Pablo Diego Hernández, Indians, 1796 - 1813 (Box 36, Folder 827)
  - José Rafael Aguirre vs. José Bermudez concerning a sum of money, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 828)
  - Will of Antonio Camacho, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 829)
  - José Fuentes Castiso vs. his wife Gertrudes Magdalena Palacios for adultery, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 830)
  - Royal decree that the oldest mayor of Puebla enforce the clause of Roque Jacinto de Ille Scasd's will that his estate be given to María de Soledad Ramirez, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 831)
  - Petition by José de la Sua Trinidad Morales, Indian, that he be released from prison, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 832)
  - Petition by Francisco de Pena Sosa that the government close the clandestine school supported by Pasenal, an Indian, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 833)
  - Complaint presented by María Gertrudis del Pino against her husband, Juan Maure, for his undesirable actions, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 834)
  - Complaint by José Antonio de los Reyes against his wife María Antonia Narcia Avila concerning her bad conduct, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 835)
  - José Mariano Roxano vs. Lorenzo Rodríguez concerning the sale of the ranch of San Lorento Astec, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 836)
  - Decree concerning case against Maríano Valeca for smuggling aguardiente, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 837)
  - Transferral of store belonging to Juan Domingo del Villar to Francisco Lamego, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 838)
  - Case concerning lease of the lands of the community of Indians, 1797 (Box 36, Folder 839)
  - Decrees concerning sale of the Hacienda San Antonio, belonging to Antonio Palula, 1797 - 1893 (Box 36, Folder 840)
  - Decree by the government that José Arreyo be set at liberty, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 841)
  - Manuela Benítez vs. Vicente Mendoza, her brother-in-law, for mistreating her sister, his wife, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 841)
  - Case concerning the ranch of Mariano José Domingues, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 843)
  - Report by Manuel Espindola, guard, concerning confiscation of aguardiente, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 844)
  - Complaint against José Guardiola for his incontinence with María de la Candelarta Ortega filed by Petra Colon, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 845)
  - Petition by Felipa de Jesús that her husband, Juan Jacinto Mejla, be released from prison, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 846)
  - Proceedings concerning the valuation of some property of Juan María López Melindo de San José, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 847)
  - Petition by María de la Luiz Palacios to the governor that she be released from prison because of sickness, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 848)
  - Petition by Antonia Gertrudis Rio Frio that her husband Pedro Martínez be released from prison, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 849)
  - Petition by José Rodríguez that he be released from prison, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 850)
  - Petition by Mariano Roman that his wife, María del Castillo, be returned to him, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 851)
  - Petition by María Gertrudis Rosas that her son, José Diego Espindola, be released from prison, 1798 (Box 36, Folder 852)
  - Petition by Domingo Saavedra to the Superior Judge concerning fishing, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 853)
  - Petition by José Solano that he be released from prison, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 854)
  - Certificate of the termination of a debt Pedro de Tierey, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 855)
  - Petition by Miguél de Urrutia concerning an unjust order by the subdelegate which he cannot carry out, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 856)
  - Petition by citizens of Xonacatlan concerning Juan Francisco de Valle, governor, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 857)
  - Case concerning extermination of tobacco of Zacatlan, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 858)
  - Concerning confiscation of aguardiente, 1798 (Box 37, Folder 859)
  - Case against José Vicente del Solar concerning management of community property, 1798 - 1801 (Box 37, Folder 860)
  - Decrees from meetings concerning the estate of Francisco García Mellado, 1798 - 1805 (Box 37, Folder 861)
  - José de Porras vs. Joaquín Losano concerning a sum of money, 1798 - 1809 (Box 37, Folder 862)
  - The province of Oaxaca vs. the estate of Rosa Gertrudis de San Miguél, wife of the late Cristóbal de Mena concerning the payment of a debt, 1798 - 1813 (Box 37, Folder 863)
  - The White Mill vs. the ranchers concerning payment for the purification of water, 1798 - 1813 (Box 37, Folder 864)
  - Petition that Joséph Joaquín Mellado be relieved of his prison sentence, 1799 (Box 37, Folder 865)
  - Case of Juan José Pena and Isabel Herrara for incontinence, presented by the former's wife, 1799 (Box 37, Folder 866)
  - María Antonia Pérez vs. Antonio Vxicar concerning his mistreatment of her, 1799 (Box 37, Folder 867)
  - Petition by María Dolores Sánchez Oresun to the government so that he investigate the immoral conduct of José Moreno, 1799 (Box 37, Folder 868)
  - Petition to the governor by José Joaquín Serrano concerning his son, 1799 (Box 37, Folder 869)
  - Petition by Ignacio de Aguilar that he be given permission to return to his native town, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 870)
  - Will of Santiago Carreto and María de la Luz Ruíz Duran, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 871)
  - Concerning the estate of Miguél Gonzáles Calderón, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 872)
  - Petition by María Manuela Hernández that she be released from prison, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 873)
  - Petition by Ramon López de Castro concerning his unjust arrest, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 874)
  - Petition by a local authority denouncing Manuel Machado for avoiding payment of a debt, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 875)
  - Petition by Rafael Marquez, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 876)
  - Petition by Ramona Moreno that her husband be granted a license, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 877)
  - Petition by Cristóbal de Pazy Pinzon that his case be dealt with so he can leave the city where he has stayed one year and two months awaiting the verdict, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 878)
  - Petition by Miguél Rafaelde Nava that two horses confiscated mistakenly because of his alleged participation in a smuggling be returned, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 879)
  - Petition by María Augustina Rodríguez that she be released from prison, 1800 (Box 37, Folder 880)